Shady Agamy

Summary

HELLO, I'M SHADY AGAMY.

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

I'm a self-taught developer. Four years ago I started front-end web development as a self-study course and learned some new technology skills. I strive to be a professional Front End web developer through teamwork and want to produce awesome real projects. I also value lifelong learning and continue to learn from eBooks and video courses from top teaching resources.

Professional Skills

- HTML/HTML5
- Pug js
- Bootstrap 3/4
- Jquery
- Redux
- · Gulp

- CSS/CSS3
- Sass
- ES5/ES6
- ReactIS
- Git

Employment History

UI developer

Freelance projects 02/2019 - 06/2019

UI Developer

Road9 Media • Cairo, Cairo Governorate 06/2019 - 07/2020

Front End Developer

EXPAND CART • 6th of October City, Giza Governorate 07/2020 - Present

Education

Bachelor's Degree

Faculty of Science Graduated - 06/2014

Languages

English

Arabic

Certificates

Udacity - One Million Arab Coders program: Front End Developer Track 08/2018.

Udacity: Intro to programming nanodegree

(https://graduation.udacity.com/confirm/URJATKHJ) 08/2018.

freecodecamp: Responsive Web Design

(https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/shady_agmy/responsive-web-design) 07/2018.

Ability to work well under pressure.

Ability to learn new tasks quickly.

Can work individually and as an effective team member.

Very good in communication and presentation skills.

Personal Data

Date of birth: 15/06/1992 Marital Status: single Nationality: Egyptian

Military service: complete with a good idol

Place of birth : Suez, Egypt Mobile Phone : +201020285787

Email: shadyagmy@yahoo.com